♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Totally ridiculous.
Wow, that was great!
I thought the special effects
were pretty good,
but, well, it wasn’t scary enough.
You’re kidding!
How come your
teeth were chattering?
For the sound effects?
Dear students,
your attention, please.
I would like you all
to give a warm welcome
to the director of the
film you’ve just seen,
and which we’ve all found
very…interesting.
And here he is now,
James Finson,
who is honoring us
with his presence today
to discuss his work in the
fascinating field of cinema.
That’s right, and I’m also here
to look for locations
to shoot for my new film.
In fact, I heard there’s an
old factory around here
that nobody uses anymore,
which I’m very interested in.
A factory?
Oh, no. Not ours!
Great! Thank you sir.
If this Finson guy finds out
about our supercomputer,
we’re in trouble.
And that means we absolutely
have to stop him from using it.
Yeah, sure we do, but how?
Nothing to worry about!
I got an idea.
How come every time he says
there’s nothing to worry about,
I get worried?
And I mean worried.
Oh, I’m so glad
to meet you, Mister Finson.
I just love your films.
I’m a big fan of yours.
Oh, really?
Well, I can’t argue with your taste!
I like my films, too. What’s your name?
Um, why don’t you just write,
“To Sissi, a rising star
who I’m going to give
the leading role to
in my next film.”
I think I’m going to write,
“To Sissi, who’s
got a lot of nerve.”
And a lot of talent!
Well, I’m very sorry, Sissi,
but the casting is over.
The parts have all been distributed.
So, better luck next time, huh?
Uh, hello, sir, the factory
you were talking about,
I was wondering, uh,
if you had already been there.
No, but I’m going to
start my scouting later today.
Well, you see, I know the place
inside out, and, uh
I really don’t think
you could find a better guide.
(CHUCKLES)
It looks like everyone
in this school has a lot of nerve!
Fantastic!
It’s even better than I thought!
Yeah, it looks alright,
but the trouble is, it’s falling apart!
Hopefully the ceiling
won’t fall on our heads!
That’s great.
I love a dangerous shoot!
That’s what I always look for--
an actor’s always
better under pressure.
Uh, Mister Finson, you’d better
watch out for your equipment.
It’s crawling with rats here!
Rats? That’s lucky!
I’ve got some big scenes
to shoot with rats in them.
Conclusion--never trust Ulrich when he
says there’s nothing to worry about.
Yeah, he tried to gross him out.
Instead, he’s even more excited.
You’re right, it’s a great set!
Too bad about all that
uranium they stored here
for so many years and years.
Maybe one day it won’t be
radioactive anymore!
Mhmm. Do you know where
this freight elevator leads to?
Oh, that old thing?
It stopped working ages ago!
Anyway, they say that
when it was working, it--
(GHOSTLY MOANING)
What was that noise?
That noise? Oh, it’s nothing!
Nothing at all!
Uh, well, there is an old rumor
that this factory is haunted by ghosts,
but I don’t believe
a word of that, although…
(CHUCKLES)
This place just keeps getting
better and better than I thought!
And you seem to know
every nook and cranny of it.
I know!
How would you like to work
as a technical advisor on the film?
Yes, do it!
Say yes, say yes!
Are you serious?
Of course I am!
Um, well, it would be
a great honor, sir!
The only problem is the principal
would never let me miss my classes.
Let me talk to him!
Sissi, your father will never
let Ulrich miss even one hour of school.
Hm. We’ll see about that.
Nothing’s gonna stop me
from becoming a big movie star.
Wow, he said no. Incredible.
I even promised to
put his name in the credits!
Uh, mister Finson?
Can I talk to you for a second?
I don’t believe it!
Sissi got a part in Finson’s film!
Yeah, in exchange for
convincing her dad to let me skip school.
Ulrich and Sissi
working together on a film!
This could be the beginning
of a great romance!
Yeah, right.
She won’t leave me alone for one second.
Your real job is
to be there in the factory
making sure that nobody
discovers our lab.
Come on, it’s not going
to be as bad as all that!
Are you sure it’s not too heavy?
When I think that I’m about
to become a big star,
and that you, Ulrich honey,
are lucky enough
to witness the event live,
oh, I envy you. I really do!
Uh, hello!
Mister Finson is expecting us.
Do you have cell phones,
by any chance?
Uh, cell phones?
Why, of course!
How could you think we didn’t?
Confiscated.
Mister Finson’s orders.
During the shooting,
it’s forbidden to communicate
with the outside world
without Finson’s OK.
That’s so there are no leaks
about the script or newspaper gossip.
That’s also why everyone sleeps here
with guards at the entrance.
Apart from all that, it’s a lot of fun.
Yes, but what if we have to
get in touch with, uh,
our parents, for example,
in case there’s a problem, huh?
When you shoot with James Finson,
there’s never a problem!
Cut off from the rest of the world!
That’s so incredibly romantic.
It’s almost like being
alone on a desert island!
Fantastic. I can’t wait.
Well, it’s time for you all
to meet the main character of my movie.
Prepare yourselves for a big surprise!
Don’t be shy.
Tell me what you think.
It’s my best monster yet, right!
And to top it all off, I’ve invented
a way to make him squirt
slimy, disgusting threads of goo.
It’ll knock your socks off! You’ll see!
Funny, but it makes me think of
the alien in that film, uh,
I can’t remember the name--
My creature is unique, young man!
And my movie will be
like no other ever made!
Hmph!
Mister Finson?
I’m very anxious to get my script,
if you don’t mind.
I’d like to start working on my lines.
You see, we professionals are very serious.
Oh, why of course!
Just one second, here it comes.
There.
Thank you.
Aaaah!
You’ve got it, kid!
You’ll be the alien’s first victim.
20 seconds on the screen, yes,
but 20 seconds of glory!
Gorey glory, too!
Hey, what are you doing in the lab?
Anything wrong?
They took my cell phone away.
Finson’s totally paranoid.
It won’t be easy staying in touch with you.
Well, well!
What kind of a weird place is this?
Hey, Ulrich,
please tell me that that wasn’t
Sissi’s voice I just heard.
Uh, Sissi, listen.
I can’t explain this to you, but uh,
you can’t tell anyone about this or else--
Or else what?
A monster’s gonna squirt
goopy goo all over my face, huh, Ulrich?
Jeremie, we’ve got
a big problem here!
Ulrich, what’s going on?
What’s that noise!
Follow me, hurry up!
Come on!
Ulrich, what is going on? Answer me!
Up there!
You’ve got to climb up. I’ll follow you.
Let’s go, we can’t stay here.
Through here, come on.
XANA’s up to something.
A tower’s been activated.
I’m launching a scan
to localize the tower.
I’ll wake Odd, call Yumi,
and we’ll be on our way.
(DRAMATIC ORCHESTRAL MUSIC)
Who’s the moron that--
Oh, it’s you, boss! I’m sorry!
Not bad, huh?
I just composed it for the film.
Okay, all you lazy bones.
Let’s go, we’ve got
a movie to make!
Go get the alien.
Boss!
Better come and take a look, uh,
we’ve got a little problem here.
A little problem, huh?
You call this a little problem!?
Go and find him, you understand!
He couldn’t have
walked out on his own!
Go find him!
Mister Finson, the two youngsters
have both disappeared.
Finson’s alien monster…It’s come alive!
How can a machine made of
plastic and rubber come alive--!
(SNARLING)
Aaaah!
I’m gonna try and find
Ulrich and Sissi.
We’ll stay in contact, okay?
Right.
Aelita?
Odd’s about to make the plunge.
How do things look?
Pretty bad.
You were right, Jeremie.
XANA is up to no good again.
I’ve localized the tower.
It’s in the polar region.
Do you really think it was
those two kids who stole the alien?
If it was them, they better hope
Finson doesn’t find them.
Okay, Jeremie. I’m in.
Aelita’s on her way to the polar region.
That’s where the scan
localized the tower.
I’ll launch the transfer.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner.
Virtualization.
Odd!
Nice little place,
but it could use a little heat.
The tower plateau is in that direction.
Let’s go. If we run, it’ll warm you up!
I don’t get this at all.
Why did he leave us alone
when he could have just as easily--
I’m pretty sure he wanted
to use us as bait to attract the others.
When you say the others, Ulrich,
do you mean the whole gang of yours?
But why?
Ulrich, Sissi!
Ah, Yumi!
Whatever you do,
don’t move a muscle!
Boy, aren’t you funny.
Oh, Yumi, I never thought
I’d be saying this to you one day,
but I’m actually very
glad to see you for once.
You can kiss and make up later.
We’ve got to go,
or XANA’s gonna get his way.
Come out of there!
And make it snappy!
Odd, Aelita, watch out.
XANA’s sent his monsters out.
Just behind you, there’s
a swarm of them armed with lasers.
20 life points per impact.
A little battle’s bound to keep me warm!
Talk about a reception committee! Wow!
Laser arrow!
Odd, watch out!
Let’s get going.
Yumi! Yumi, can you hear me?
Where are you?
Come on, answer me, Yumi!
Please answer!
Tell me right now!
What have you done with my alien!
Huh?
But w--
Let’s go!
Boss! Did you find the--
Don’t let them get away!
Get a move on!
Stop! I created you!
You have to obey me, you hear!
Jeremie, it’s Yumi.
Yeah, I did find them,
but XANA’s taken possession
of a monster who’s gonna be here--
Odd, Yumi and Ulrich
are in big trouble.
There’s not much time!
Wow, that sure is steep.
But we have no choice.
Yahoo! Ha-ha! Incredible!
Wow, what a fabulous ride!
Ha-ha-ha!
Woo-hoo!
Hey, I think I just might
settle down and live here!
Yeehaw!
Aaah!
By the way, Jeremie,
what’s at the end of this?
Well, I uh…
Oh, I get the idea.
Geronim-o-o-o-o-o!
At any rate, the tower
is pretty close now.
Thanks for the info, Jeremie.
You think he’s called it quits?
I doubt it.
For once I have a chance
to show how how talented I am,
and that mechanical monster
has to go nuts!
And what’s more,
he decides to pick on me!
I don’t understand!
What did I ever do to that plastic
piece of junk to deserve that, huh?
Hey, Ulrich, you think you could
get her to keep still for a second?
Shh.
Well, Aelita, any sign of that tower yet?
Yes, but I may be seeing double.
Jeremie, there are two towers!
How can that be?
I only saw one on the holomap.
XANA must’ve
done that to confuse us.
Well, we’ve gotta choose one.
And pronto, too.
Hello, Jeremie?
Well, have you got any news for us?
Yumi, what’s going on?
Answer me, Yumi.
Yumi! Yumi--
Odd!
I know what you’re gonna tell me--
“Hurry up!”
Well, for your information,
we’re not exactly
having a tea party here!
Get down!
Aelita, you’ve got to choose
one of the towers now.
I can’t hold them off much longer.
Okay.
Laser arrow.
Yahoo!
Take that!
Oh no, I’m out of arrows.
Here I go.
Jeremie,
if I happen to choose the wrong tower,
it’ll be all over, you know that.
I have faith in you, Aelita
Ulrich!
Jeremie, I’m sorry.
I chose the wrong one.
No! Wait!
Return to the past now.
Great idea to use
the factory for a movie.
Thanks.
I must confess that my ideas are,
I say this with great modesty,
absolutely ingenious. Here.
It makes a great set.
By the way, you do know that
a film was shot here once before?
You’re kidding.
No, a science fiction movie.
With an alien!
And a fabulous picture, too!
No, no. I’ve given it some thought,
and I don’t think
the factory’s a good idea.
Besides, it wasn’t my idea
in the first place!
What’s that?
How dare you accuse me
of lying to you!
I can find another producer, you know!
I am not upset!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO